foreign
because of this mosque
you have the north of the Quran
through the Quran is the Lord of God
and to come to the conclusion
that celebration can be attained only by
worshiping God Alone
question
we come to the conclusion after that
nothing but
we must be absolutely positively
worshiping God alone and we must realize
that only God possesses the power to
benefit you or harm you that only he is
worthy of worship that everyone ends
in the past Generations his death
helpless all of us whether it is
Muhammad or Jesus or Mary was dead you
are useless they are powerless they are
helpless and that's what the Quran says
we come to that conclusion
and
we've had some strange opposition
because of that strange opposition I'm
going to leave the latest
of the important support that we get
this one is really enthusiastic
and uh
I look forward to meeting the new and
brothers discovery
here's a my humble opinion the most
important event in the history of Islam
in the last 1000 years
so we do need this support once in a
hurry however I'm surprised because
it's not supposed to be appreciated
until about three or four generations
from now the present generation usually
contemporary Generations usually do not
appreciate
a great discoveries but I don't claim
any parts of it because God's will to
bring it to the world at this time now
we've come to this conclusion as a very
small minority
to the extent that this is probably the
only mosque in the world
the only
commemorates
God alone and no other names are
mentioned but
which is in agreement with the
Commandments of Quran that must belong
to Allah Paul and anyone else when the
message
with God do not call on anyone who will
judge means with
just uh since we are such a small
minority and the vast majority of
Muslims are not
an agreement would also assist the ones
who haven't read by the way the only
opposition we ever had is from people
who did not raise the Earth We're never
ready
the demon will do not know
this has been the only opposition and
these 20 people
no matter they they read it or know
about it they completely
go to the exact opposite because they
ought to make up for the first
opposition so so we become enthusiastic
support
but the question is
are all those millions of Muslims wrong
and you are right this is the important
question that you must face this is the
question that will be asked to you
those Scholars
millions of Muslims and generations of
Muslims are they wrong to follow and not
to follow the Quran and Rome and you are
right
this is the question I want to address
in this book
and there's an equally important
question
those Millions upon millions of
Christians
and Christian's covers are they all
wrong
when they say Jesus Son of God or Jesus
God or Jesus part of Eternity
you are right and all those millions of
Christians and millions of
generations of Christians are they all
wrong
an important question isn't it
before I go any further I want to tell
you one thing if you worship God alone
you can never be alone
because this is the whole purpose of
life
on the other side
we can say they may be right but maybe
they're right okay but this is a maybe
and to find out if it's a maybe right or
maybe wrong you have to wait for the
Iraq to find out now if you're willing
to take that chance I am not
so the question will want to deal with
now is are those Millions upon millions
of Muslims wrong and you are right
are those Millions upon millions of
Christians wrong can you arrive
18.
yeah let's go to the top of the page
page one or three at the 14th this is
the the fall of Satan
certain set respite me till the day of
Resurrection
God said you are responded Satan said
since you will that I go astray I will
always stop on your straight path and
mislead them then I will come to them
from their front from behind them from
the right and from the left and you will
find most of them unappreciative
God said you are evicted from despise
and the base
those who follow you will join you in
hell
now let's move on to so we have Satan's
pledge to mislead us all
and he is very powerful I want to tell
you later on here as to how powerful I
think you can hold the whole earth in
his hand
the whole planet Earth in his hand he
was God's assistant
and he wants to do
God's
parents and serve God so God gave him a
lot of power this will make him think he
can be a god with God
I think I'm not sure that you can
manipulate the thoughts of every human
being on Earth at the same time
simultaneously dignity
to misgive us all but there is
very strong we're up against that
terrible enemy but also when is the
worship of God and all he cannot touch
you because God puts guards on you or
more powerful than him than it says and
they keep him away
you know that from the Quran but let us
go on to Surah 11 verse 119.
thank you
there's 155
only those endowed with Mercy from your
Lord will not dispute
and this is what he created them for
your Lord's decision has already
I don't know why I'm a couple of verses
off let me see
just go back to 116 and don't see it and
find out if only the papers and Russians
had some intelligent people who enjoined
them from corruption they would have
been safe but we served a few of them
while the rest pursued their material
things and became Sinners your lord
never destroys any Community unjustly
why the people are righteous
have your Lord will he could have made
all the people in one congregation he
could have been all believers
but as it happens the majority are not
believable or they are believers who
friend and I don't worship
I do not wait he could have made all the
people running congregation but they
were always dispute only those endowed
with Mercy from the Lord will not
dispute and this is what he created them
for so the purpose of our creation is to
differ
your Law's decision has already been
made that I will fill geanna of both
genes and humans this is the part I
wanted you to hear
that you lost decision has already been
made God already saw the day of judgment
and you saw that the vast majority of
people are going to help
this is in studying the question are
those Millions upon millions of Muslims
right wrong
are those Millions upon millions of
Christians right or wrong
um the Muslims fell in the same trap as
the Christians but in the same problem
they cannot worship God Alone they have
to mention other names with God
next I want to look at 12103 these are
the famous verses that you know one one
or three
the repetition helps you remember this
you can discuss it with anybody one or
three says
under the subtitle the majority of
people will not believe
majority of people no matter what you do
will not believe
so this is the majority of people to
start with the minority We Believe
all right let's go on even though you do
not ask them for any weight for this is
a message to all the people and even
though the heavens and the hills are
full of signs they pass by them totally
heedless and now listen to this the
majority of the minority
the minority of the minority attains
salvation so now we see the majority of
people disbelieve and now we have a
minority of believers
the majority of Believers are going to
help that's what the Quran says one hour
says and the majority of those who
believe born into idol worship
these are famous verses that you should
memorize by heart you know 123 and 12 1
6 that the majority of people will not
believe
and then the majority of the minority
the majority of the Believers will fall
into idol worship and will go to hell
because either worship is not forgivable
and I want to clarify here either
worship at the time of death
if the person dies in a state of idol
worship
you cannot be forgiven
but if you if you discover that you're
an idol worshiper and you repent and you
pledge you'll never do it again then it
is wiped out because this is the whole
idea of our existence is to come to the
conclusion that only God is to be
worshiped
these are shocking facts
now the millions upon millions of
Muslims
who do not believe God when he says the
Quran is complete
they believe in God they really do
and they pray the five prayers
they pray them to God
but they idolize Saints or the prophet
so they have fallen into idol worship
and this is a statement of fact in one
number six that the majority of
Believers will fall into either Wars
so you have to be in an extremely
positive minority
and extremely apportionate person with
an extreme minority
to really make
and that's That's what Satan did to us
let's go on to 32 verse 13.
Surah 3 2
verse 13 1-3
that's the button page two eight three
had we will we could have given guidance
to everyone
but it is already predetermined that I
fell help with gems and humans all
together
another statement to try it is already
predetermined God already saw the day of
judgment and got so early that the
majority of people flanked as
disbelievers and the majority of
Believers flunked as other worshipers
let's go on through 36 7.
it's 300 it says it is already
predetermined that the majority of
people will not believe
and we go on to 38.85
don't see this
every point
substance 313
I will fill hell with you and all those
who follow you
let me go back to
78.
75 let's go back to 75 God said o Satan
what prevented you from prostrating
before my creation are you too arrogant
or much too hard
Satan said I am better than me you
created me from fire and created him
from clay
God said then you must get out for you
are rejected
you have deserved my curse till the day
of judgment Satan said my Lord respite
me till the day of Resurrection God said
you are respected until the specified
time 82 Satan said I swear by your
majesty that I will mislead them all
accept your servants who are absolutely
devoted to you alone
these are the ones that Satan cannot
touch was the military who decided God
alone and you decide you believe God you
have guards on you who are more powerful
than Satan and they will keep him away
so let me read this again
83 accept your servants who are
absolutely devoted to you alone
God said the truth is and I utter only
truth I will fill help with you and all
those who follow you
that's the vast majority of people
Millions upon millions of Christians and
Muslims and Jews
so you see in the Quran that it is a
statement of fact so when you think in
your mind when I tell you those Millions
upon millions of Christians on the Iran
and you arrive
God tells you yes they are wrong
if they idolize Jesus they are wrong
they idolize anyone or any saint or
anything
they are wrong
and if they are in this state they have
to go straight to hell
and this is what we saw was versus that
we just looked there
and the same is true with the Muslims
Millions upon millions of them do not
believe God when he says the Quran is
complete and we are told in Quran that
the seals fall in them definite spots in
their ears and they cannot hear the
message they have they are not allowed
to understand the Quran
and we have people here saying that you
have to know Arabic to know the Quran
and I saw them personal Quran that says
no you didn't have to go out of it says
well it says it is available only to the
Believers
the sincere believer
as for the disbelievers they are blind
and deaf to it this is Surah 41 verse 14
4. 144
so it has nothing to do with language
God puts the Quran in the person's heart
now those Millions upon millions of
Christians and millions upon millions of
Muslims
is that unjust
why are they all gone what is God saying
because already predetermined I would
put head from all of them
we know about this gracious and merciful
God calls himself the most merciful of
all the merciful ones
that is the most merciful so why is all
these people gone to hell
is he unjust
God says in the Quran that he does not
inflict an atom's worth of Injustice
you see this is the airport's choice
in fact they insist on it
God puts fences between them and hell
and they goes up defense they insist on
planning defense God puts barbed wire on
top of the fence and those makes it
impossible for the human being to go to
hell and they insist that the god they
scratch themselves and go up the press
to drop in hell that's what they do
you better see it right now
let us look at 7 172.
thank you
it's the choice that the people insist
from seven 172.
that spins one one
six
months of God our natural instinct
record that your lord gathered all the
descendants of Adam before creation and
had them bear witness on themselves
saying Allah am I not used more
they said yes indeed we bear witness
therefore you cannot say on the day of
Resurrection we we never knew about this
nor can you say it was our parents who
set up idols and we followed in their
footsteps you know this is what they
taught us because my parents taught me
that's why you teach us that but that is
not an acceptable excuse
so God put an instinct in us to worship
him alone
just like the bird
who told the bird to sit on their eggs
until they had
do the birds go to school
what what makes the bird the mother
burnt and the father will come back and
feed those the babies
you know they sit in the nest of the
mouth like this
and there comes the mother of the father
and they said what makes them do that
didn't go to school you have no
certificates but God put the Instinct in
them and God put in us the instinct to
worship him alone
so God is just when we are the guys
Muhammad was Jesus of Mary or Saints we
go against our instinct
have you tried to chase a birth away
from the edge
she refuses
because that again is her Instinct our
instinct is to sit on the action that
they had and you've got tested all right
if you try to take the eggs then they
will come and pick you and especially
it's in a big powerful bird
laughs
so it is their Instinct and to prove it
once again let's look at 30 30.
that's the problem page 277
under the subtitle monasteryism is
Natural Instinct
let's start at 28 God sides here in an
example from among Europe would you
share your assets with your servants to
the extent that you become equal and to
the extent that you respect them as they
respect you now
think of your boss at work
is it gonna give you enough
responsibilities that you will be equal
to you
you equal to him
we thus extend the revelations for those
who understand indeed the wicked follow
their own opinions without knowledge can
anyone die both misguided by God no one
can help them Theory they don't want to
look at therefore you shall devote
yourself completely to the revision of
monotheism this is the natural instinct
this is the natural instinct that God
implanted into the people
nothing can change such creation of God
this is the perfect religion but most
people do not know
did you see that instinct this is the
natural instinct that God put in US is
God just
or is he not just
this why God says that he does not
implant an atom's weight of Injustice
because he put in us the Instinct before
we were before we can prepared to this
world
you're putting us the one God to worship
one God
and when we go and idolize Jesus or
Muhammad we are going against our
instinct
let us look at 7 179.
verse 179.
so we have assigned to help multitudes
of gems and humans this is the idea that
they started the football with
we have assigned to help multitudes
Millions upon millions of genes and
humans they are the ones who have hearts
that do not understand eyes that do not
see
and ears that do not hear they are like
animals no they are even worse they are
unaware
so they do not think
see what's wrong with us in this mask
we used our brains that's what we
thought we did not accept what was given
to us from our parents our ornament
so-called Scholars and so forth we used
our our brain and this is the
Commandment in Quran in Surah 17 36
let's look at it 1736
he built 190.
do not or you shall not accept anything
that you yourself cannot ascertain you
are given the hearing the eyes and the
mind in order to examine and verify
you are responsible for because God is
wrong so remember the last verse verses
they have how children do not understand
eyes they do not see and here's with
which they do not feel
I mean here God is telling you you shall
not accept anything until you are
positive that it is correct because you
are having a Salvation on it it's your
neck
you are the one who will go to heaven or
to help
so when you hear anything from anyone
you have to ascertain and make sure that
it is right
whether it is your parents your holama
your president
your wife your husband
whatever it is you have you must
ascertain you must be absolutely
positive because you are the one who
will go to heaven with him it is your
neck
the relations who have real mothers
fathers children and all this it's just
a means of reproduction here but we are
all independent individuals when we go
there hereafter
now
okay
of using our minds
and it has to do with our particular
situation here where we follow or not
follow at this or Sunday
we take the example though the Salat
prayers the most important worship
there are millions upon millions of
Muslims create the noon in the afternoon
silently
rakas number three and four are also
silent in Mother's Day
okay
this is millions upon Millions if you go
to a person mosque in Cairo and Craig
alone in the loud voice you will have
join a hip of conversion who I'm telling
you wrong
anywhere anywhere in the Muslim world
you go right here in Tucson to the
Islamic Center in and out boys they will
come and correct you
anywhere and this is this is the only
mosque in the world who will pray the
noon and the loud voice
or the Aston and not allow boys but in a
in an audible voice now why there's a
commandment to Quran that says now they
when you ask them why do you do that
question and they came up with the
prophet said and the scholar said
they'll give you that Sunnah business
so now God gave us the brain and he gave
us eyes and ears as you see in this
verse
70 36
we have to think there's a commandment
of Quran that says you shall not break
silently
you shall not pray too loud or silently
but seek an intermediate tone
now we see in the Quran in several
verses the prophet says I am afraid to
disobey my Lord I'm afraid of a terrible
the retribution of a terrible today
put in yourself so the prophet himself
is order to say therefore and also
logically the prophet will not disobey
God we need
see they are the people who claim to
follow and love the prophet the
Christians claim to follow and love
Jesus and the Muslims claim to follow
Allah
but they are the first ones who read the
key on him and disobey him
will he disobey God
this is the command of the Quran Surah
17 verse 110 you shall not very silently
a commandment
is it is it possible at all that the
prophet disobeyed that and paid silently
so we have to use our brain and this is
why you saw in the in the 7172 that
these people are going to help because
they have hearts or Minds with the words
they do not understand
eyes University do not see and hear the
risk we do not fear it doesn't take too
much thinking using the brain
to know that it's impossible for the
prophet to disobey
God they disrespect the prophet
I didn't I didn't intend to say this but
I'm going to say it one of the things
that they said and they uh they said
it's a religious order is that polygamy
is limited by Paul
now the prophet one the prophet might
allowed to explain that
they read all the spark when they
explained that because a polygamy is not
limited in Poland maybe situations in
the future well whatever you must be
awesome everyone must have 100 wives I
don't know
we don't know what the situation is
polygamy is not
limited the Quran
anywhere
but they limit this and they have
hundreds of Hadith studying here is
limited by four
and they forget
they forget that their Idol
against his will the verification of
Muhammad against his will they forget
that he left my anointed that
and then they turn around to say he knew
the future
well some somebody will tell you he
married this before the Commandment came
so which is not true because the the
verse that they abuse in Surah women
that's two three or four
then stop because because the rest of
the Fall there's not a limitation
because the person is not going to say
two three or four or five or six or
seven or eight
[Music]
forever I have to start somewhere it did
not say it is limited by four
but when they did this that verse came
early in Medina and the prophet married
women after that in fact most of them he
made it after that verse came down
so they have no way around it but they
are
the people to insult the prophet and
disrespect him and disobey him
one more thing that I didn't intend to
say the other day they were telling your
own you follow the Hadith of the Prophet
anyways
when you when you pray you read the
fatah and this is Hadith is the problem
now you have to be very alert here
it's true
will follow the true Hadith of the
Prophet that came out of Muhammad's
mouth we follow the Quran this is the
proven hadees of the Prophet the only
Hadith and the Quran says that says this
is
we don't follow the Hadith of Muhammad
that came out of his mouth the Quran
now what they think is the Hadith of the
prophet
of things that are attributed to the
prophet I'm laughing because yesterday
we grabbed one of the epoxy Hadith and
where the Hadith and the sun rises
between two horns of the devil so don't
pray
so what they think is Hadith and of
course we went through the series of
narrations
with all the funny names in it you know
but we heard from
this person that he heard from his
father that he heard from his great
great uncle that he heard from somebody
that that the prophet said he said that
the prophet said
yes
you guys are following the Hadith
story to tell us who told you that
Muhammad sent us air Generations ago
one of the things that they will try to
get you where there's a classic one
foreign
but this is an old one
because it's uh it insults your your
pride you know but also uses the same
thing we're using you would say Do not
worship anyone besides God
but you know something
worshiping the Imam or the scholars
there is an established by the
Washington Quran is a fact
people do worship their Scholars
the demands of priests or rabbis or
whatever
you want to call it I'm not putting
myself in any of those categories but
I'm just using because to answer their
arguing now I want to do not to see it
in the Quran 9 31.
right verse 31.
tonight
they attacking their priests and rabbis
as Lord besides God
as well as Christ the son of Mary they
were commanded not to worship but the
one God there is no God except he much
too glorious to have purpose
so how do we know we did not fall in
this same thing okay one thing we do on
this mask is when we test the questions
we test the issues and we attack them
and we
of literacy
it doesn't matter what the issue is
and this is the essence of freedom you
must be free to test any question and
solve them you must never have any doubt
in your heart
and how do we know that we live
important this child they have taken the
priests and rabbis
and they can add to this and imams and
Scholars and all of us as God besides
God
this is a step forward what this means
they can't prostrate before the priest
or Rabbi or Imam or scholar
some people think on the other side that
the worse it means before the
development for prosperity
but that's not it
the Criterion is that we must know and
we must distinguish whoever will prevent
that trap or not
if
various colors for the priest or the
rabbi or the Imam or the anime or
whoever it is is saying something that
is exactly identical to What God Says
and you thought of that you are not
taking off the scholar of the Imam or
the priest or the rabbi as a God you are
not worshiping the priest or the rabbi
or the man or the strong
but if
a scholar
or the Imam or the rabbi or the priest
says something that is different from
what God's hand and you follow that
and instead of following God then you
accept saying that as a god besides God
not only that you you set the Imam or
the scholar or the priest or the rabbi
as a God in his head of God
now God said You shall not very silently
and the scholar said you said very
excited
now who is your god you see what the
verse says line 30 one
if
the Imam or the scholar is saying
something different from what God Said
and you follow that then you are
worshiping amen
this is your criteria
but when
the The Scholar or the priest of the
rabbi or the Imam is saying something
that's identical to what God said you're
bound to obey accident obedience is
required as you know from the story of
Moses and his people Moses are prophet
and without showing us a prophet not
just any human being one of the great
ones
and the attitude obedience was demanded
because if any one of us of us tells me
or tells you you shall worship God Alone
obey him or her
foreign
and it is not worshiping that person at
all
you are worshiping God
and you are following those words
because they are the words of God not
because the words of the scholar or the
man
so the Muslims Millions upon millions of
them have taken their Scholars as God
besides God
I can give you hundreds of examples
because I'm right here in the Quran
and this one is a good one the one that
presented us very discussing between one
he said why do you pray that no one in
the afternoon silent day when God said
You shall not flame silently
it's because they have taken their
Scholars as God
besides God
so what they are what they tell you
you're worshiping but they're really
looking in the mirror see it's what they
have
it's something that they are doing they
are taking their Scholars under a man
as God beside God
they would always try to
get you this is a classic and we're
gonna go fast through this verse 790.
you have to get used to move
them getting you in many different
stories look at certain mind people
again
one more line
the elders will just believe among these
people said if you follow us right
you'll be a loser
and even more profoundly scored a 40
verse 26 40. 26. we're gonna laugh at
this one
page 3 23.
what versions
Pharaoh said nothing to kill Moses and
let him implore his Lord I feel lest he
offers your religion or spreads
corruption on Earth
this is terrible speak he's afraid more
than with also the relation of the
Egyptians
or spread corruption on Earth
and they will always tell you this they
will tell you if you want to drive alone
you're going to be a losers you're going
to corrupt your religion you're not
Muslim even go to that extent you're not
Muslim you also God Alone
you know
very very fine the prophets Jesus of
Muhammad against the world and freedom
from Quran
smaller 25 verse 31 that Muhammad will
disowned them from the day of God
and we learned from Matthews in the
Bible 7 23 the Jesus
oh okay